this is some view up here yeah as long as you and i are friends then as far as i'm concerned
i don't need anyone else i'll always be here by your side even if the whole world turns its back
on you don't say things like that it's so embarrassing hey i think you should have a
nickname what do you want me to call you a nickname huh what about sora
you should call me taka
you're so slow taka
no fair wait up
another dream
you're such a slow poke
no i'm not i'm fast i'm fast
so weird i can't remember
you
only one more week of summer vacation left but i've been a good student and i'm almost done
with all of my prep work i forgot to tell you i heard about a summer festival that is starting
tomorrow at the shrine near the toya shopping district a festival huh and is that all i don't
understand is there a reason you're telling us that well i'm pretty sure i saw a flyer hanging
somewhere on my way to school yesterday and i didn't know if any of you guys had heard yet
thanks for passing that info on i guess i was hoping you were gonna suggest we all go to the
festival together why in the world would i ever waste my time going to a stupid overcrowded event
like that rika's with you there a couple of years ago rika decided to go to the biannual anime
festival in tokyo thinking it might be a lot of fun but boy was she wrong the train was so cramped with
people rika could barely move she got off at the halfway point and went home rika learned her lesson
no more festivals i've actually heard of that festival people say it's ridiculously crowded
because it's the only place you can buy these exotic special edition books as big a fan as you
are i'm surprised you didn't stick it out are you questioning rika's fandom right now that really
chaps her hide and making a girl's hide chapped is not a very gentlemanly thing to do there's no need
to drag this conversation into the gutter do you know who you're speaking to without the gutter rika
has nothing left you could talk about science or all your inventions or how you're a cool girl with
awesome glasses you really should give yourself more credit rika needs her glasses to learn science so
she can sell her inventions in order to pay for her expensive smut habit this is who rika really is
besides rika has plenty of contacts in the anime world because of her scientific capabilities so
she gets special edition volumes whenever she wants in fact the only reason she works with these
companies in the first place is for all the free cartoon porn i'll never doubt your fandom again i can
tell you that much for sure tell you uh hey kotaka huh at these festivals do they sell food
because if they have octopus dumpling booths i'm in i'm not sure about octopus but there's plenty to
eat there wait do you actually like octopus dumplings why you don't i do those dumplings are
my favorite way back when i was a little kid in osaka i didn't really fit in with the people around
me and i guess you could say i was a bit depressed but my dad used to bring me home these octopus
dumplings from this famous store and it became my comfort food they say octopus dumplings every day
keeps the depression away they're great although i can't stomach those bastards who sell crappy octopus
dumplings with a straight face hey calm down it's just food i agree they're super yummy but it's not
worth working yourself into a frenzy over they taste really good let's just leave it at that okay
huh i love them so much if you want to buy me some as a present i would totally let you
do you really want me to get you octopus dumplings dumplings rule big bro if she gets them then i get
them too looks like it's a done deal then we're going to the summer festival yeah octopus is probably
against your religion maybe you should stay home freak big bro and i are going alone you vampire scum
you should stay home don't ruin our date i want to go yeah dumplings would hit the spot same here
i'd like to come if that's all right with you of course so that brings our group to five people total
how fun just hold your horses i'm not gonna be the only one to miss out guess that makes it seven
i thought you two didn't like crowds we like octopus dumplings
all right now that's a commitment to food if i've ever seen it
hmm
hey here early as usual rika look what you can do when you put your mind to it
huh is that some kind of backhanded compliment if you're gonna be insulting just come out with it
i think you look really nice thank you very much that's such a lovely thing for you to say
you're going to make rika blush i guess i can't win with you can i since we're just missing me
there's no point waiting around let's move out she'll have to catch up to us trying to leave me
behind are you you're so rude that figures never can be too careful around you well i'm here now so
let's get this party started shall we
what the heck was that for don't worry about it come on guys let's go hey wait for us
what's the matter with you kodika it's tradition for girls to wear yukatas to summer festivals
so why didn't you make kobito wear one it's not like she's required to wear a yukata i mean look
at yozora she didn't wear hers please let's not bring commoners into this listen i want to see kobito
wearing one of those robes right now i hate to disappoint you but kobito doesn't own a yukata
kodika rika has good news there's a shop right here where you guys can purchase whatever you need
that's perfect you want to wear a yukata just like the rest of us girls don't you
what do you say we give it a shot try some on
okay let's make it quick though i'm hungry for octopus
i hope you have to spend the rest of eternity in there and never get to eat oh yeah
eat this blood sucker they'll never give up yukimura go on ahead and buy some dumplings so we
can avoid all this drama that sounds like a plan and thanks for trusting me to be your gopher i won't
let you down you should probably buy one too thanks for the advice but i'm okay your good looks are
you're only redeeming quality you know you really should take advantage of that
yeah sin is right a yukata would really compliment your long beautiful hair don't you think
uh no thank you but that's not really my style
too bad she won't wear one i bet she'd look beautiful big bro
she's so cute she's just adorable oh i want to gobble her to pieces i think you look great
she looks better than great she's the cutest little thing i've ever seen in my life and
you better be nice to her and tell her as much or else do you understand me
you heard me tell you i loved it right but you on the other hand you look completely ridiculous
with your pudding colored hair clashing with that robe my hair specifically the color you're a
laughingstock at school literally everyone makes fun of you maybe you should try making it black
funny you should mention that i've actually considered dying it a different color before
but the thing is my mom's hair looked just like this and she's gone oh right you see for the most
part i'm a spitting image of my dad but the hair is my mom's sometimes i wish i looked more like
kobito she's got her face her hair and basically everything else too since my hair is the only thing
i got from my mother that you can tell by looking at me it'd be way too difficult to ever let it go
dying it another color would feel like turning my back on where i came from and who i really am
they can make fun of me but i like my hair because it always makes me think of her
that's so cool there's no question you're way different from the other boys at school
come on let's go have fun
ready to go
hey we've been looking for you sorry we're so late
no way it's so good it's rude to talk with your mouth
these octopus dumplings are amazing you're so tiny how can you eat that much i think i've died and gone to food heaven
be ladylike that is no way to eat rick is practicing her erotic eating techniques on this banana
are you getting turned on not at all no here have some of mine
no
something's not right here you go sorry to keep you waiting oh that's okay
for you hey thanks a lot let's see here i wonder how this one will taste
well what do you think is it good it's got a light fluffy texture but the thin skin ruins the whole experience
plus there's not enough octopus meat inside it sucks this is all my fault gross come on you guys let's all look for a better octopus dumpling stand
help me out i think i've had enough rika feels the same sounds great i'm still hungry i want to eat that thing that looks like a cloud
thanks for buying me all that food everything was awesome yeah i'm completely stuffed after that
but hold on you guys you said you wanted to eat delicious octopus dumplings didn't you if i eat more i'll puke
then why the heck did we come here in the first place i think we've all had plenty to eat right everyone
let's go home good idea no you can't leave yet you're not the boss of us okay meat besides what else is there to do here
no one's leaving till i say so yeah you can't go we're here we might as well stick around and play games
if you want to scoop up goldfish and throw rings like a little child you can be my guest hey i'm not a little kid
i just like to have fun i was going to ask you to compete against me in a head-to-head festival gaming
competition but since you're a chicken i won't waste my breath i already told you there's nothing i hate
more than being around a massive crowd but i'm not afraid of you meat besides this place compared to how
crazy the pool was the other day it's a piece of cake i think it's about time i give you a little reality
check what do you say well i suppose i'll let you try so what game should we play first i'm an expert
at scooping goldfish what i mean to say is i challenge you to a goldfish showdown
i hate to break it to you but when it comes to goldfish i'm the queen of the pond sorry to
shadow your delusion but the only thing you're queen of is the moron time to find out who's number one
here's your money sir thanks here you go thank you go hey it tore this is all a rip off yeah because
it's made out of paper the idea is to catch a fish without tearing it crap come on just stop moving so
i can catch you you stupid little goldfish after i win i'm gonna make you pay me back for all the money
it'll cost me to beat you in this dumb competition i'll take ten more please sure thing
all right that's cheating you can't do that i prefer to think of it as sound strategy i'm real
sorry miss but i don't allow cheating at this booth take a hike before someone sees you and i can let you
off the hook this time be thankful i rescued you fishy i've decided i'm gonna call you condada from now on
you're lucky you made it out of there alive me we're gonna do that next
it doesn't matter what we play because in the end you're going down try not cheating this time
let's go okay you're on you're nuts come on why don't you leave those two alone and come play some
games with us that's way too simple you idiot sounds fun awesome yay i'm gonna play with my big bro
check it out my water balloons way bigger than yours is well mine's a whole lot prettier so i guess
i win you big stupid face ha ha ha come on you seriously think you beat me with that crap anyone
with eyes could see i dominated you back there your umbrella looked like a spaceship
you're pathetic meat i'm not cut out for puny detail work like that anyway right there let's settle
this at the roulette wheel wait sauce rice crackers oh fine
rika did good wow nice shot okay here special prize hey guess what rika already has this gaming
system so she's gonna give it to you as a present please think of rika whenever you play it and let
her know if she can help you out hmm wait why don't we put it in the club room
oh yeah that sounds like a good plan boobs that was a dirty trick oh shut up a win's a win don't be
a sore loser how can you call that a win you jerk hey you two get the hell out of here
take one thanks a lot rika really appreciates it there you are i've been looking everywhere for you
we're going to need somebody to help with all the stuff we've won these stupid prizes are really
getting in the way of our showdown so we want you to carry them right now
no i can't i've got my own things here what is that a game system but how this is all courtesy of
bullseye rika oh neither of us came out on top true but if we would have kept playing until the
bitter end i feel confident i would have won that's crap and you know it did you forget i'm ahead by one
win dummy please the goldfish scoop doesn't count because you cheated hey let's go find yukimura and
the girls i'll be waiting at the west gate of the shrine so stella said she was cool to come get you
mm-hmm but because of all the festival traffic she told me she doesn't know how long it's going to
take her to get here oh well since we're killing time why don't we go shoot off some fireworks they
have tons for real sounds like fun besides summer's almost over this could be your only opportunity
this is totally awesome i've never shot off actual fireworks before let's do this thing
okay i'll buy a bucket and some candles
here we go
wow it's on fire it's really on fire you guys
now gaze upon my secret fire magic technique church lady burn in the fire of purgatory and
die in obscurity megiddo flame
i know that chick too stop it no copying me
so cool rika will take up an interest in fireworks after this
our lives are exactly like these sparklers they shine on big and bright but the beauty of it only
lasts an instant before it dies out completely
oh triple sparklers oh grow up free as child's play
well we saved the best one for last this is gonna be incredible
incredible
that's it
an utter disappointment just like our friend meet there and what exactly do you mean by that
right when i'd given up on it completely it comes through in the end
yeah like me that comment wasn't about you in any way whatsoever
look it's still going rika thinks we're getting our money's worth
hmm
hey guys is it me or does something stink you're right rika doesn't think that's gunpowder either
oh
yosara it's your hair
it's on fire stop drop and roll
quick we need water
hurry
turn around yosara
good job you put it out
yosara are you all right
good
no
that poor thing
for the rest of summer vacation we didn't see yosara at all
not once
she didn't even show up to the club
donna bay
here
suda
asagawa
yeah
here asawa
here
ujioka
origuchi
here
well you made it in the nick of time if i were you i'd take a seat
yes sir
one
ah
sora
It's been a while, Taka.
She's right.
Ten long years feels like forever.
So after the Summer Festival fireworks incident,
Yozara didn't show up at the club like usual.
Ah, the club room is so much more relaxing
without that stupid vixen hanging around.
Chill out. That's not a nice thing to say, you know.
Sorry, the truth's the truth.
Ah! This is a problem for me!
I need Yozara here or I'll go nuts!
Just tell me what's the matter.
She's how I get my potato chips!
Oh, right.
Next time, folks. We don't have many friends.
You know, without her here, it's actually so relaxing.
I'm kind of bored.